The 80's were brilliant, if you were in charge.
The Devil's Double is a drama, action, thriller film directed by Lee Tamahori.
A chilling vision of the House of Saddam Hussein comes to life through the eyes of
the man who was forced to become the double of Hussein's sadistic son.
Latif Yahia / Uday Hussein, played by Dominic Cooper.
Sarrab, played by Ludivine Sagnier.
Munem, played by Raad Rawi.
Saddam Hussein / Faoaz, played by Philip Quast.
Kamel Hannah, played by Mem Ferda.
Ali, played by Mimoun Oaïssa.
The Devil's Double is a 2011 English-language Dutch-Belgian biographical thriller film directed by Lee Tamahori, written by Michael
Thomas, and starring Dominic Cooper in the dual role of Iraqi military commander Uday Hussein and his body double Latif Yahia.
It was released on 22 January 2011 at the 2011 Sundance Film Festival and was released in limited theaters in
the United States on 29 July 2011 by Lionsgate and Herrick Entertainment to mixed critic reviews.
The film explores themes of palace, impostor, pervertion.
The tone is emotional and intense.